>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 好的，让我们谈谈这次提升的运动。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: All right, let's
talk about this exercise on hoisting.
这里有一个内联函数表达式。
We have a inline function expression here.
我在演讲中说我通常使用一个班轮功能
And I said in the lecture that I
typically do use one-liner functions
作为内联函数表达式。
as inline function expressions.
但为了这次演习的目的
But just for
the purposes of this exercise,
当我们把它作为函数式表达时，让我们看看它的样子。
let's see what it looks like when we move
it out as an in-function expression.
然后你就可以自己打个电话
And you can then make calls
on your own as to whether or
而不是提高或阻碍可读性好吗
not that improves or
hampers the readability, okay?
所以我可以把它拉出来
So I can pull that out,
我必须将其保留在此作用域内，因为它确实引用了 studentId。
I have to leave it inside of this scope
because it does reference the studentId.
我不能像个独立助手一样把它拉出来
I can't pull it out as
some standalone helper,
它在使用 studentId时关闭。
it is closed over in using the studentId.
但是有一件事我喜欢这种把东西拉出来的风格
But one thing that I do like about this
style of pulling things out as function
声明。
declarations.
这些功能被用来做这些功能的地方
Is that the places where these functions
are used end up reading a lot more
完全不需要中断函数执行，定义代码。
cleanly without being interrupted with
function execution, definition code.
这就很干净了
So this reads very cleanly as find,
通过匹配标识，按标识查找学生记录。
by matching the ID,
find a student record by ID.
所以那种把东西拉出来的代码
So that style of code
of pulling things out,
即使是一个胆，从可读性的角度来说，也有一些优势。
even one-liners, does have some advantages
from a readability perspective.
好吧我们在这里做个类似的事情
Okay, let's do a similar thing down here.
我们已经使用了一个指定的函数，那么这一功能又如何呢 ?
We already have a named function being
used, so what about this function?
我们知道那个功能没有在内部使用任何东西
Well, we know that that function's
not using anything internally, so
我们可以将它作为它自己的独立功能
we could pull it out as its
own standalone function.
因此，我会这样做，而我们亦会以名义上的名称来作参考。
So I will do that, and
we will simply reference it by name.
再一次又有了可读性的好处
Which again, has that readability benefit,
现在最清楚的事情是什么
now it's much clearer
what the sort is doing.
与 printRecord 相同， printRecord 本质上是独立的
Same thing with printRecord,
printRecord is essentially a standalone
可替换为引用它本身的名称的函数。
function which can be replaced by
a name that references it itself.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 现在，显然意见不一，但
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Now,
obviously opinions vary, but
我的意见是制作更多可读的代码来完成这个操作。
my opinion is that produces a lot
more readable code to do that.
再向下 paidStudentsToEnroll ，我们具有内联过滤器功能。
Down to paidStudentsToEnroll, again,
we have an inline filter function.
这是直接插入过滤器功能
This is inline filter function is not
使用任何内部变量。
using any of the internal variables.
等等什么叫什么叫 " 针刺 " 一样的东西
So wait, what was that called,
needToEnroll, same thing,
它可以被移出
it could be moved out.
正如我在练习中所说的我们更喜欢的原因
And as I said in the intro to the
exercise, the reason why we can prefer,
从功能提升的角度来看。
from the perspective of function hoisting.
我们更喜欢把它移到外域的原因是它更容易，
The reason why we can prefer moving it
to the outer scope is that it is easier,
一般在拍板时分析范围。
generally, to analyze scopes
when they are flatter.
嵌套式范围越深，
The more deeply nested scopes get,
在我们预料不到的地方会发生更混乱的封锁
the more confusing the closures can happen
in places that we're not expecting.
所以我们试图把他们转移到一个可以尝试的范围之外
So we're trying to move them out to
as outer of a scope as we can to try
要有一个更简单的范围模型来思考
to have a simpler scope
model to think about.
好吧 getStudentId 是一个类似的东西
Okay, getStudentId is a similar thing,
它不是指内部的任何东西，所以
it is not referring to
anything internally, so
就是， >> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 我们可以走出去。
that is,
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: One that we can move out.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 最后，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And then,
finally, the remindUnpaid,
我们有这个过滤功能
we have this filtering function.
这又不是什么内部的事
Which is, again,
not using anything internal,
这样我们就能把它拉出来用它的名字
so we can pull it out to this
outer scope and use it by name.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 最后，我们可以看到所有这些功能都在顶部。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Lastly, we can see
that all these functions are at the top.
但由于功能提升，它们不一定要在顶部。
But they don't necessarily need to be at
the top because of function hoisting.
我们要做的就是复制所有这些
So what we're going to
do is copy all of those,
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 然后过来
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And come down here and
把它们放在底部
put them at the bottom.
然后就为了普通的可读性，我喜欢画 ASCII 线。
And then just for general readability,
I like to draw ASCII lines.
这条线下面的所有东西都是执行细节
And everything below the line
is implementation detail,
所有上面都是我的可执行代码
everything above the line
is my executable code.
所以当我打开文件时，我看到最上面的所有东西都在运行。
So when I open the file, I see everything
right there at the top that's gonna run.
正如我在演讲中提到的，我认为这基本上是理解
As I mentioned in the lecture,
I see this as essentially understanding
更详细的关于我的工具的事情
something more detailed about my tool.
用我的工具，我认为会产生积极的变化，在这种情况下，
And using my tool in a way that I think
effects a positive change, in this case,
用于可读性。
for readability.
因此，可以使用提升和使代码更容易混淆的方式。
So there are certainly ways that you can
use hoisting and make code more confusing.
但这并不意味着所有吊装过程都很糟糕。
But that doesn't mean that all
usages of hoisting are bad.
我觉得有办法用吊装和使用功能声明
I think there are ways to use hoisting and
use function declarations and
使用已拉出的嵌套函数或函数。
use nested functions or
functions that are pulled out.
我认为有一些方法可以使您的代码更便于阅读。
I think there are ways to do that in which
you can make your code more readable.
希望你能从这次演习中得到这个消息
Well, hopefully that's the takeaway
you get from this exercise.
这是一个值得你去分析你的代码的风险。
Is that that's a worthwhile venture for
you to analyze about your code.